-Hi! -Hey!
-嗨 -嘿
So, what's the final head count on my baby shower?
有多少人會來參加 寶寶的歡迎會？
About twenty. Couple people from work had something else to do.
大約有20個人 有些同事有事沒辦法來
Your sisters called and can't make it.
你的妹妹們打電話來說她們沒辦法來
What? You mean they're not coming to a social event..
什麼？ 你說她們不來參加…
where there's no men and no booze? That's shocking.
沒有男人跟酒的社交聚會？ 那真的是太稀奇了
I don't care, as long as my mom's here.
我不在乎，只要我媽能來就行了
-Oh, my God. Your mother. -What? My mom's not gonna be here?
-天啊，你媽 -什麼？我媽不會來嗎？
Well, given that we forgot to invite her, it would be a big coincidence if she was.
說不定我們忘了邀請她 反而能讓她鬆口氣
My God!
我的天啊
Phoebe was in charge of the invitations.
不是我的錯 菲比負責發請帖的
I don't have a mother. So often I forget..
我沒有媽媽 所以我常忘了…
Oh, give it a rest.
得了吧
So my mother is not coming to my baby shower?
我媽媽不來參加 寶寶的歡迎會？
No.
對
Neither is mine.
我媽也不會來
We'll take care of it. We'll call her. You go home and get ready.
我們會處理的，我們會打電話給她 你先回家做準備
Make sure she comes. It's important. It's my mom.
確定她一定會來 這很重要，她是我媽
-I know. What's her number? -I don't know.
-我知道，她電話號碼幾號？ -我不知道
Go. I have it in my book. Go.
你去吧，我記在我的電話簿裡了
If you're in charge of invitations, why am I calling her?
如果你負責寄請帖 為什麼是我打電話給她？
Hello, Mrs. Green! Hi, it's Monica Geller.
喂，葛林太太 嗨，我是摩妮卡蓋勒
-Oh, hello, Monica. -Hi.
-哈囉，摩妮卡 -嗨
It's last-minute, but we've decided to throw an impromptu..
這是緊急通知 我們打算在今天…
-baby shower for Rachel today. -My daughters told me..
-幫瑞秋的寶寶辦歡迎會 -我的女兒們已經告訴我了…
when they received their impromptu invitations a month ago.
她們在一個月前 就接到歡迎會的請帖
-Okay, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. -For what, dear?
-好吧，我很抱歉 -為什麼呢？親愛的
For not inviting me, or for lying about it?
為了沒有邀請我 還是你說謊騙我呢？
Oh, my God! My ass is sweating.
天啊，我的屁股在流汗
I'm sorry for everything. Really, I mean..
我為所有的事道歉 真的，我是說…
there's a lot of planning in a baby shower.
計劃寶寶的歡迎會 真的累人
You know, things get overlooked and..
我們會忘了一些事 還有…
Phoebe's mother killed herself.
菲比的媽媽自殺了
Why? Did you forget to invite her too?
為什麼？ 你們也忘了邀請她？
Oh, you're so funny.
你真是幽默
Please, please, can you come? It starts at 4:00.
拜託，你能來嗎？ 歡迎會四點開始
-Well, all right. I'll see you at 4. -Thank you.
-好吧，四點見 -謝謝
-Isn't it at 3? -Son of a bitch!
-不是三點開始嗎？ -混蛋
The One With The Baby Shower
本集播出：寶寶歡迎會
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey, Joe! Wanna shoot some hoops?
喬伊，你要去打籃球嗎？
And for the record, I am not covering the tall one this time.
我得告訴你 這次我不要防守那個高個子
Fine, but she's not that tall.
好吧，但她沒有那麼高
I can't go. I'm practicing. I got an audition to be the host of a new game show.
我不能去，我在練習 我要參加新遊戲節目主持人的試鏡
-Cool! -Great!
-酷啊 -太棒了
If I get it, by day I'll be Dr. Drake Ramoray.
如果我能當上主持人 白天我是德瑞克拉莫瑞醫生
But by night I'll be Joey Tribbiani!
但晚上我是喬伊崔比亞尼
You'll be perfect for this! That's already your name!
你非常適合這份工作 節目名稱跟你的名字一樣
I know. I know.
我知道
It'd be great if I got this because you never know what could happen on a soap.
我能夠得到這份工作是最好的 因為誰都不知道演肥皂劇結果會怎麼樣
But I could be a game-show host forever.
但我可以一輩子 當遊戲節目主持人
Like that Bob Barker guy. He's been doing The Price is Right for 75 years.
就像巴伯貝克 他主持猜價遊戲75年
I bet the ratings weren't good for the first 25.
我敢說前25年的收視率 一定不太好
You know, before there was television.
那時根本沒有電視機
But the problem, this game is really complicated.
問題是 這項遊戲真的很複雜
Come on. You said the same thing about Hungry Hungry Hippos.
少來了 你也那麼說飢餓河馬
And last week, you beat Ben.
上星期你贏了班
Yeah. I have to be honest with you guys.
對 我得跟你們承認
He kind of let me win.
他有點放水讓我贏
The audition's in a couple hours, and I don't understand the game.
再過幾小時就要試鏡 我搞不懂這個遊戲
Do you want some help?
你需要幫忙嗎？
Oh, really? That'd be great. Hey, you guys can be the contestants!
真的嗎？那真的太棒了 你們可以當參賽者
We can lose to junior-high girls some other time.
我們可以下次 再去打敗國中女生
All right. Let's play Bamboozled!
好吧，我們來玩暈頭轉向
-Bamboozled? -Yeah. Isn't that a cool name?
-暈頭轉向？ -對，那個名字很酷吧？
-Yeah! -No!
-對 -不
All right. Okay. Our first contestant is Ross Geller.
好吧 第一位參賽者是羅斯蓋勒
Tell us about yourself, Ross.
做個自我介紹吧，羅斯
Well, I'm a paleontologist. I live in New York.
我是古生物學家 我住在紐約
I have a son, Ben. Hi, Ben! And..
我有個兒子叫做班，嗨，班，還有…
I said, a little bit, Ross. How about you, Chandler?
我叫你介紹一下自己，羅斯 你呢？錢德
I'm a headhunter. I hook up out-of-work Soviet scientists..
我是個尋人專家 我在找為卑鄙的第三世界國家…
with rogue Third World nations. Hi, Rasputin.
失業的蘇聯科學家 嗨，拉斯普廷
Excellent! Let's play! Chandler, you'll go first.
太棒了，我們開始吧 錢德，你先
-What is the capital of Colombia? -Bogota.
-哥倫比亞的首都在哪裡？ -波哥大
It's Bogota, but close enough.
是波格大，但很接近了
You can either pass your turn to Ross or pick a Wicked Wango Card.
可以把機會讓給羅斯 或挑魔法機會牌
-What does a Wicked Wango Card do? -I should know that.
-魔法機會牌可以做什麼？ -我早該知道的
Let's see. One moment, please..
讓我看看，請等一下…
Here we are. A Wicked Wango Card determines if you go higher or lower.
好了，魔法機會牌 能決定你要向上或是向下
Higher or lower than what?
什麼東西向上或是向下？
-This is embarrassing! -Can you believe how lame this is?
-這真的是太丟臉了 -你能相信這有多爛嗎？
I'm sorry. I don't believe contestants are allowed to talk to each other.
抱歉 我想參賽者不該交談
I told the stripper to be here at 5. That's good, right?
我叫脫衣舞男五點要到 那很棒吧？
You ordered a stripper for the shower? That is inappropriate.
你請脫衣舞男來寶寶歡迎會？ 那太不適當了
Why? He's gonna be dressed as a baby.
為什麼？他會打扮成寶寶的樣子
Oh, hi, Mrs. Green. I'm so glad you could make it.
嗨，葛林太太 我很高興你趕來了
Thank you so much. We're so sorry. We could not feel worse about it.
謝謝你，我們很抱歉 我們真的很過意不去
Try.
試試看吧
There's my little girl!
我女兒在那邊
-She's still mad. -Yeah, I know.
-她還在生氣 -對，我知道
Isn't it great? One less person to make small talk with.
那不是很棒嗎？ 少了一個人跟你咬耳朵
Hey, how are you?
你好嗎？
Yeah, yeah. Okay, okay.
對，好吧
Phoebe, Sandra's mad at you too. It doesn't bother you?
菲比，珊卓拉也在生你的氣 你不會感到困擾嗎？
We've apologized twice. I can't do any more than that.
我們道了兩次歉 我真的沒辦法了
You hate it when people are mad at you..
你討厭 別人生你的氣…
but you just have to be okay with it.
但你得去 接受它
Okay. I can do that.
好吧，我辦得到
-I gotta go powder my ass. -Oh.
-我得去幫我的屁股撲痱子粉 -喔
Look at that face! Just like when you were in high school.
看看你的臉 你跟念高中時還是一樣
If I didn't know better, I'd say you were a cheerleader in trouble.
要不是我很瞭解你 我會以為你是個有麻煩的啦啦隊員
-Come, let's get some tea. -Okay.
-來吧，我們去喝點茶 -好吧
Oh, my! Look at that. Only three weeks to go.
天啊，你看 只剩三星期了
Did you pick a nanny? If you use your housekeeper, it will split her focus.
你挑好奶媽了嗎？ 如果請管家兼職，她會分心的
Actually, I'm not gonna use a nanny. And I don't have a housekeeper.
事實上我不請奶媽 我也沒有管家
It's like you're a cave person.
你好像山頂洞人
You must get a nanny. You don't know how overwhelming it will be.
你得請個奶媽 你不知道帶孩子有多累
When you were a baby, I had Mrs. K.
你小時候我僱用了K太太
Mrs. K! Oh, yeah, she was sweet. She taught me Spanish.
K太太，對，她人真的很好 她教我西班牙文
I actually think I remember some of it.
我想 我還記得一點
Tu madre esta loca.
（西班牙文）
Such a sweet woman.
她真是個好人
And more important, she became a part of our family.
更重要的是 她成為我們家的一部份
That's right, Mrs. K. What did that K stand for?
沒錯，K太太 她到底姓什麼？
I have no idea, dear. She was the nanny.
我不知道，親愛的 她只是個奶媽
As great as she was, I can't afford that.
她真的很棒 我出不起那筆錢
I'm sorry. Sometimes I forget not everyone has alimony.
抱歉 有時我忘了不是大家都有贍養費
-Oh, Rachel! -What?
-瑞秋 -什麼？
I just had a great idea! I'm gonna come live with you!
我想到一個好點子 我要搬過去跟你們住
What? What?
什麼？
Oh, I'm so happy I'm gonna do this for my little girl.
我很高興 我能幫我女兒這個忙
Look at you. You have tears in your eyes.
看看你 你感動的都快哭了
Yes, yes, I do.
沒錯，我是快哭了
Ross, you're in the lead.
羅斯，現在是你領先
Would you like to take another question or spin the Wheel of Mayhem?
你要再回答一題 或旋轉處罰輪？
The Wheel has not been my friend tonight, Joey.
今天我轉輪子的運氣不太好 喬伊
I'll take another question.
我要再回答一題
Okay. This is gonna be tough. Hold your breath.
好吧，這題很難 仔細聽好了
It's okay. I'm ready.
沒關係，我準備好了
You gotta hold your breath until you answer.
你得注意聽 再回答問題
This is ridiculous! He's not gonna hold his..
這太可笑了，他沒辦法注意…
Okay. What do you have a fear of if you suffer from this phobia? Triska..
好吧，如果你害怕恐懼的感覺 那該怎麼說？懼…
Holy cow. That's a big word. Trisk..
天啊，那個字真長，懼…
Look at this. How do you say that?
看看這個，它該怎麼念？
-Let me see that. -This one right here.
-讓我看看 -就是這個字
-Triskaidekaphobia. -Fear of Triscuits!
-懼13症 -害怕樹上
-No! No. Fear of the number 13. -Fear of Triscuits?
-不，是害怕13 -害怕樹上？
It's possible. They have really sharp edges.
這有可能 它們真的都尖尖的
Chandler, you're up.
錢德，輪到你了
I'm entitled to use my Angel Pass for a free turn.
我要用天使通行證 換免費的機會
Yes, yes. But you can only use it once, so choose wisely.
對，但你只能使用一次 請考慮清楚
This is tricky.
這真的很難決定
I mean, I am in the lead, but I would love another shot at the Golden Monkey.
現在是我領先 但我想再試一次金猴
-This game makes no sense! -You're upset because you're losing.
-這個遊戲真的很沒有道理 -你很生氣是因為你輸了
Oh, come on, Ross. I think we're all losers here.
少來了，羅斯 我想我們都是失敗者
I would like to hang on to my Angel Pass please.
我想用 我的天使通行證
You can either spin the Wheel or pick a Google Card.
你可以選輪子 或選張搜索牌
Let me think, let me think. Oh, I don't care.
讓我想想 我不在乎
You must choose.
你非選不可
-Either. It makes no difference. -Choose, you jackass.
-那還是沒有差別 -快選吧，混蛋
-I'll take a card. -You picked the Gimme Card!
-我要抽卡片 -你選到了給我卡
-You get all of Ross' points! -What?
-你拿到羅斯所有的分數 -什麼？
This game is kind of fun!
這個遊戲開始好玩起來了
You don't think it's crazy that you get my points..?
你不覺得你拿到我的分數 太瘋狂了…
The contestants aren't supposed to speak to each other.
參賽者 不該交談的
Now, do you wanna start opening presents..
你要開始 拆禮物了嗎？
because it seems like people are getting itchy to leave.
因為大家 似乎急著想離開
And when I say people, I mean me.
我說大家 指的是我自己
-Why did you invite my mother? -What?
-你為什麼要邀請我媽來？ -什麼？
She wants to move in with me and Ross to help take care of the baby.
她要搬過來跟我和羅斯住 以便幫忙照顧寶寶
-For how long? -Eight weeks.
-多久？ -八星期
I love my mother, but, my God, a long lunch with her is taxing.
我愛我媽，但是天啊 跟她一起吃午餐太久就是種折磨
I'd be honored if she wanted to live with me.
如果她想跟我住 我會覺得很光榮
She can't hear you.
她聽不到
What am I gonna do?
我該怎麼樣？
If you don't want her to move in with you, just tell her.
如果不希望她搬過去 你該直說的
You're right. I'm about to have a baby.
你說的對 我就快生了
I can say I don't want her sleeping on my couch.
我可以說我不希望 她睡在沙發上
She'll wanna sleep in my bed. This can't happen.
她會睡在我床上 絕不能讓那種事發生
That is right.
沒錯
Tell her you don't want her to live with you.
告訴她 你不希望她搬過去跟你們住
Do not take no for an answer.
別讓她拒絕你
This is great! Now she's gonna be mad at Rachel!
這真的太棒了 現在她會生瑞秋的氣
And I'm just gonna swoop in there and be like the daughter she never had.
我要跑過去 當她的乖女兒討好她
Oh, honey, you have to let it go.
甜心 你得忘了這件事
Okay.
好吧
Who doesn't accept an apology?
誰不會接受道歉呢？
I mean, it's just so simple.
那真的很簡單
"I'm sorry, Sandra." "That's okay, Monica.
「對不起，珊卓拉」 「沒關係，摩妮卡」
I forgive you.
我原諒你
And by the way, you're very pretty."
還有，你非常漂亮
I have new respect for Chandler.
我真的要很尊敬錢德了
All right, everybody! It's time to open the presents!
好了，大伙們 該來拆禮物了
Yes! The first gift that Rachel opens..
對 瑞秋要拆的第一樣禮物…
should be from the grandmother.
應該是外婆送的禮物
Because you're the most important person in this room! And in the world!
因為你是這裡最重要的人 也是全世界最重要的
I don't have a gift because I wasn't invited until the last minute.
我沒有準備禮物 因為我在最後一分鐘才被邀請
But thank you so much, dear, for bringing that to everybody's attention.
但非常謝謝你，親愛的 讓大家都注意到這一點
How about you less important people? Let's open your presents!
你們這些不重要的人呢？ 我們來拆你們的禮物吧
-It's okay that you didn't get a gift. -I kind of did.
-你沒準備禮物也沒關係 -但我也算是送了你一樣禮物
Me! Eight weeks of me.
我要跟你同住八個星期
Okay. See, Mom, the truth is, I can do this on my own.
好吧，媽媽 事實上我可以自己照顧寶寶
I know you're gonna be a terrific mom.
我知道你會是個好媽媽
But you need help at the beginning.
但一開始你需要幫忙
I know what I'm doing. I can handle it.
我知道我在做什麼 我應付得來
Really? Remember Twinkles?
真的嗎？還記得亮亮嗎？
He was a hamster. I'm not gonna vacuum up my baby!
他是只倉鼠 我不會拿吸塵器吸我的寶寶
Okay, come on, Rach. It's present time!
快來吧，瑞秋 拆禮物的時間到了
You're the glue holding this party together.
你是 這個派對的主角
It's kind of falling apart here.
現在這個派對也快毀了
-Oh, look! -Wow!
-你看 -哇
This is from your friends at work.
這是你同事送的
Oh, my gosh! Oh, wow! Oh, I know what this is.
天啊，哇 我知道這是什麼
Wait a minute.
等一下
That can't be right.
不可能
Is that a beer bong for a baby?
這是寶寶的啤酒機嗎？
Darling, that's a breast pump.
女兒，那是擠奶器
Did I say I was done guessing? Okay, thank you for that.
我說過我不再猜了嗎？ 好吧，謝謝
Oh, wow! What's this?
哇，這是什麼？
-It's a Diaper Genie. -It dispenses clean diapers!
-它是尿布精靈 -它是用來放乾淨尿布的
It's where you put dirty ones.
那是放髒尿布的
Why don't you take it outside and throw it in a dumpster?
我為什麼不直接 把尿布丟在外面的垃圾桶？
-You're gonna do that 10 times a day? -What, it goes 10 times a day?
-你每天要丟十次嗎？ -什麼？寶寶一天可以拉十次？
Are we feeding this baby Indian food?
我們得餵她印度食物嗎？
No, dear. That's what babies do.
不，寶寶都是那樣的
Rachel, listen to your mother. She is very smart.
瑞秋，聽你媽媽的話 她非常聰明
What will you do with the baby while you trot out to the garbage?
你去倒垃圾桶時 寶寶要放在哪裡？
I don't know, I'd leave it on the changing table?
我不知道 把她放在尿布台上？
-What? What did I do? What did I do? -You can't leave a baby alone.
-什麼？我做了什麼？ -你不能丟下寶寶一個人
Of course, I know that!
我當然知道
Of course you never leave a baby alone.
千萬不能 丟下寶寶一個人
It would.. She wouldn't be safe.
它會… 她會不安全
Not as safe as she would be with me, the baby dummy.
她跟我這個菜鳥媽媽在一起 也不會安全
Opening the presents is a little overwhelming right now.
現在拆禮物 太刺激了
I'm gonna maybe open them all a little bit later.
我待會 會把它們都拆開
Thank you for coming, for the gifts..
謝謝你們趕來 還送了禮物…
-and this basket is beautiful. -It's actually a bassinet.
-這個籃子很漂亮 -它是搖籃
Okay, Mommy, don't ever leave me.
好吧，媽媽，別離開我
In what film would you hear this line: "We don't need no stinking badges!"
你會在哪電影聽到這句台詞？ 「我們不需要臭警徽」
-Treasure of the Sierra Madre! -Correct! Backwards Bonus.
-《碧血金沙》 -答對了，倒念還能加分
-Madre Sierra the of Treasure! -Yes!
-沙金血碧 -對
What? There's extra points for that?
什麼？那樣子可以加分？
Fair not that's!
平公不
I'd like to go up the Ladder of Chance to the Golden Mud Hut!
我要爬上機會梯 到金泥屋去
-Wise choice. How many rungs? -Six!
-聰明的選擇，幾階？ -六階
-That noise can only mean one thing. -Hungry Monkey!
-那個聲音只代表一個意思 -飢餓的猴子
-I'd like a Wicked Wango Card. -It's an audio question.
-我要魔法機會牌 -這是聲音題
Name this television theme song:
說出這出電視劇的主題曲
Oh, my God. I know this. Give me a second.
天啊，我知道 讓我想一想
-Tell it to the Time Turtle! -Shut up!
-去跟時間烏龜說吧 -閉嘴
-"I Dream of Jeannie"! -Yes! Back in the lead!
-《太空仙女戀》 -答對了，你再度領先
I'd like to spin the Wheel.
我要轉輪子
Oh, come on!
快點
Super Speedy Speed Round.
超級快速回合
-Is there a Hopping Bonus? -Of course.
-跳躍有加分嗎？ -當然
-Who invented bifocals? -Ben Franklin!
-誰發明了雙焦點透鏡？ -班法蘭克林
Correct. Which monarch ruled Great Britain the longest?
答對了 哪個君王統治英國最久？
Queen Victoria!
維多莉亞女王
You forgot to switch legs between questions. No Hopping Bonus!
你忘了換題時要換腿跳 跳躍動作沒加分
Every time!
每次都這樣
-Yeah. Now over to Chandler. -I'd like a Google Card.
-對，現在輪到錢德了 -我要搜索卡
-Are you sure? -Yes! No! Google!
-你確定？ -對，不，搜索卡
Oh, my God! Congratulations, Ross! Because, Chandler..
天啊，恭喜你，羅斯 因為錢德…
-you've been Bamboozled! -No!
-你已經出局了 -不
-Yes! -This is the best game ever!
-對 -這是我玩過最棒的遊戲
You'll stay as long as I need you?
只要我有需要，你就會留下來？
-Of course. -I swear I'm not an idiot.
-當然 -我發誓我不是白癡
I read books on pregnancy and giving birth.
我看了 懷孕跟生產的書
I didn't think to read about what to do when the baby comes.
我沒有看 帶孩子的書
And the baby's coming..
寶寶出生後…
and I don't know what to do. Oh, can I throw up in my Diaper Genie?
我不知道我該怎麼辦 我可以吐在尿布精靈裡嗎？
Sweetie, you're gonna be fine.
甜心，你會沒事的
-Where you going? -I'm going to the bathroom.
-你要去哪裡？ -我得上洗手間
Now, don't worry. Everything's gonna be okay.
別擔心 一切都會沒事的
It is gonna be okay!
會沒事的
Worth a shot.
這值得一試
Hey! Why are you all red and sweaty?
你幹嘛滿臉通紅全身是汗？
I just Bamboozled Chandler!
我剛剛幹掉了錢德
Which is not a sexual thing.
我沒有對他不軌
-Well, that was a quick shower. -Not if you were here.
-歡迎會這麼快就結束了 -因為你沒來
Looks like we got a lot of good stuff.
看來我們收到不少好禮物
We did. My mom got us the greatest gift of all.
沒錯 我媽送給我們最棒的禮物
A Play-Doh Barbershop?
培樂多理髮師工具組？
No. She's going to live with us for eight weeks.
不，她要搬過來 跟我們住八星期
What?
什麼？
Yes! She's gonna help us take care of the baby!
對 她要幫我們照顧寶寶
You're not serious!
你不是認真的
She's a very nice woman, but we can't take eight weeks of her.
她是個好人 但我們無法忍受她八個星期
-She'll drive us crazy.. -Hi, Ross!
-她會把我們逼瘋… -嗨，羅斯
Hey, roomie!
嘿，室友
Hey, I'm Ray. I'm the producer of the show.
喬伊，我是雷 本節目的製作人
It's a pleasure to meet you, Ray.
很榮幸能見到你，雷
This is Duncan and Erin. They're gonna help with the audition.
他們是唐肯跟艾玲 他們會幫你試鏡
-Right, Ray. -Whenever you're ready.
-對，雷 -你準備好了就開始
Hello. I'm Joey Tribbiani. Let's play Bamboozled!
哈囉，我是喬伊崔比亞尼 我們來玩暈頭轉向吧
Erin, first question. In hockey, who is known as "The Great One"?
艾玲，第一個問題，在曲棍球史上 誰被稱為是「偉人」？
-Gretzky. -Correct!
-葛瑞斯基 -答對了
Want to pick a Wicked Wango Card or spin the Wheel?
你要挑魔法機會卡 或轉輪子？
Didn't your agents give you the revised rules?
你的經紀人沒有給你 改變過的遊戲規則嗎？
We've eliminated all that. No wheel. No cards.
我們把那些東西都刪掉了 沒有輪子或機會卡
Why?
為什麼？
It was too complicated. People didn't follow it.
那太複雜了 觀眾沒辦法瞭解
Complicated?! Spin the Wheel to go up the Ladder of Chance..
複雜？ 轉輪子上機會梯…
through the Rainbow Ring to the Golden Monkey.
穿越彩虹環 找金猴
You yank his tail, and you're in Paradise Pond!
拉它的尾巴 就能到天堂池
Yeah. All that's gone.
對，那些都刪掉了
It's a simple question-and-answer game now.
現在這只是個 簡單的問答遊戲
Well, what's fun about that?
那有什麼好玩的呢？
You expect me to host a boring game of people answering questions?
你要我主持 觀眾回答問題的無聊遊戲？
Women in bikinis hold up the scores.
會有比基尼女郎拿得分板
Let's play Bamboozled!
我們來玩暈頭轉向吧
So I thought we'd put the changing station in the living room.
我想我們該把尿布台 放在客廳裡
I thought I'd bring in my decorator because I feel like I'm at my best..
我想請我的設計師過來 因為我覺得我最擅長…
when surrounded by jewel tones.
把房子弄得珠光寶氣
Sure, who doesn't?
當然，誰不是呢？
Oh, and all those dinosaur knickknacks you have..
你買的那些 恐龍小玩意…
they might be more at home in the garage.
它們或許比較適合 放在車庫裡
-Well, we don't have a garage. -Did I say garage? I meant garbage.
-我們沒有車庫 -我說車庫嗎？我是說垃圾桶
You know what? Maybe it's not absolutely vital that you live with us.
你知道嗎？ 或許你不一定要跟我們住在一起
-Well, Rachel needs help with the baby. -I really do. I don't know anything.
-瑞秋需要人幫忙帶孩子 -真的，我什麼都不會
I'm sure that's not true.
我相信那不是真的
Oh, no? Do I know anything about babies?
是嗎？ 我會帶孩子嗎？
-No. Not a thing. -It's frightening.
-不 -那真的很可怕
Even if she doesn't know anything, I do.
就算她不會 但是我會
And I'll be there to show her.
我會教她
That's exactly what Rachel's father told me.
瑞秋的爸爸 也是那麼告訴我
Know what he said at the first 3 a.m. feeding?
你知道第一次半夜三點起來餵奶 他說什麼嗎？
"I'm tired. You take care of it."
「我累了，交給你吧」
Which I later said to him when he wanted to have sex.
後來他想跟我求歡時 我也是那麼告訴他
Well, I'm not Rachel's dad.
我不是瑞秋的爸爸
And no offense, but he's an ass.
我沒有惡意 但他是個混蛋
I do like you, Ross.
我真的喜歡你，羅斯
I have a son. His mother and I didn't live together.
我有個兒子 他媽媽跟我沒有住在一起
When he was with me, I took care of him all the time, by myself.
他跟我一起住時 我都是自己照顧他
-That's true. You do have another child. -Yeah.
-沒錯，你還有一個孩子 -對
With another woman.
跟另一個女人生的
Have you no control, Ross?
你沒有自制力嗎？羅斯
That's a different issue.
那是另一個問題
The point is, when the baby comes, I will be there to feed her..
重點是寶寶出生後 我會幫忙餵她…
and bathe her and change her.
幫她洗澡換尿布
I want to do all those things.
我願意照顧她
-You don't need me to live with you. -Yes!
-你們不需要我搬過去 -對
Yes. You're gonna be so missed.
對，我會想念你的
-You'll be a great father. -You'll be a wonderful grandma.
-你會是個好爸爸 -你會是個好外婆
Hello? I still don't know what the hell I'm doing!
哈囉 我還是不知道我該做什麼
Every first-time mother feels that way.
新手媽媽 都會有那種感覺
You're gonna pick it up. Hey, you will. Look, when you first came to the city..
你可以慢慢學，你會的 當你剛到紐約來時…
you were a spoiled, helpless little girl who used Daddy's credit cards!
你是個被寵壞的無助小女孩 只會用爸爸的信用卡
I hope you're going somewhere with this.
我希望 你真的有話要告訴我
Look at you. You're this big executive.
看看你 你現在是個大主管
You are more capable than you give yourself credit for.
你很能幹 證明了自己的能力
I have no doubt you're gonna be an incredible mother.
我相信 你會是個好媽媽
-Really? -I'm telling you.
-真的嗎？ -沒錯
Thank you.
謝謝
All right. I'm gonna get going.
好吧，我得走了
No, sweetheart, stay put.
不，甜心，別送了
I'll let myself out. It's like I'm not here. Which I almost wasn't.
我自己出去，就當我沒來過這裡 我差點真的來不了
You're just so funny. You're so funny. What do I do?
你真的太幽默了 我做了什麼？
Nothing. You have apologized to her, like, a million times.
沒什麼 你跟她道歉很多次
And she's been nothing but terrible to you.
她只是 無視你的道歉
You just threw her daughter a lovely, albeit slightly boring, shower.
你讓她女兒辦了 一個可愛無聊的歡迎會
-And she hasn't even thanked you for it. -You know what? You're right.
-她甚至沒有謝謝你 -你知道嗎？你說的對
If you wanna say anything, I'd tell her off.
如果你有話要說 快告訴她
Really?
真的嗎？
Okay, I will.
好吧，我會的
Mrs. Green?
葛林太太
It is rude to leave a party without saying goodbye to the host.
不跟主人道別 就離開派對是很無禮的
When someone apologizes to you, the decent thing to do is to accept it.
如果有人跟你道歉 你得接受
What I did wasn't on purpose.
我不是故意要那麼做的
But what you're doing to me now is plain spiteful.
但你對我的態度 太可恥了
-Spiteful? -That's right.
-可恥？ -沒錯
It's time you took a good look in the mirror, young lady!
你該好好去照鏡子 小姑娘
Old lady!
老太婆
Lady!
女士
Wrap it up. Wrap it up. Wrap it up.
別說了
So whenever you're ready to apologize to me, I will forgive you.
只要你準備好跟我道歉 我會原諒你
Good day.
再見
I can't feel my legs!
我的腳沒有感覺
You were fantastic! I'm so proud of you.
你真的太棒了 我非常以你為榮
-Yeah? I'm proud of me too. -You should be.
-是嗎？我也以自己為榮 -你應該的
-Could you get me something to drink? -You got it!
-你能幫我拿杯飲料嗎？ -沒問題
Mrs. Green? Okay, I'm really sorry! I apologize. If you..
葛林太太，我真的很抱歉 對不起，如果你…
Okay! I bit my tongue!
好吧，我咬到舌頭了
But I'm still really sorry!
但我真的很抱歉
-Okay, I'm ready. -You sure?
-好吧，我準備好了 -你確定？
I've done my studying, and I know my stuff.
我看過書 把一切都弄清楚了
All right, then.
好吧
Rachel Green, let's play Bamboozled!
瑞秋葛林 我們來玩暈頭轉向
How do you test the temperature of the baby's bath water?
你該如何測試 寶寶洗澡水的溫度？
-Put your elbow in it. -Excellent!
-用手肘去試 -非常好
-How do you put a baby down for a nap? -Full, dry, on its back, no loose covers.
-如何讓寶寶小睡一下？ -餵飽她，換干尿布，趴睡，被子蓋緊
Correct!
答對了
There's a hopping bonus here, but I don't suggest you take it.
這題有跳躍加分 我不建議你那麼做
Okay.
好吧
This is an audio question. What do you do when a baby makes this sound:
這題是聲音題 寶寶發出這種聲音時你該怎麼辦？
Check if it's wet or hungry, burp it.
檢查她是尿濕或餓了，幫她拍背
Excellent! Now do you want another question or a Wicked Wango Card?
太棒了，你要再回答一題 或抽魔法機會牌？
-A card! A card! I pick a card! -Oh, I'm sorry.
-我要抽牌 -對不起
You've been Bamboozled! You're gonna be a terrible mother!
你出局了 你會是個爛媽媽
I've lost sight of why we're doing this!
我忘記我們為什麼要這麼做了
Please don't walk away.
請不要走開
I've gone too far.
我說得太過火了